<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Arvin Jagayat - Personal Website</title>
    <link>https://arvinsroom.github.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Arvin Jagayat - Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://arvinsroom.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://arvinsroom.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arvinsroom.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Arvin and I&amp;rsquo;m happy you cared enough to click and learn more about me!
Academic Background I did my Specialized Honours BSc in Psychology at York University, completing my undergraduate thesis under the supervision of Dr. Jennifer Steele at the Interpersonal Perception and Social Cognition Lab. During my time at York, I also had the pleasure of volunteering as a research assistant in Dr. Joni Sasaki&amp;rsquo;s Culture and Religion Lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>https://arvinsroom.github.io/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arvinsroom.github.io/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://arvinsroom.github.io/curriculum-vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arvinsroom.github.io/curriculum-vitae/</guid>
      <description>Download CV You will soon be able to download a copy of my curriculum vitae here. Stay tuned!
Select Publications Choma, B. L., Hodson, G., Jagayat, A., &amp;amp; Hoffarth, M. (2019). Right-wing ideology as a predictor of collective action: A test across four political issue domains. Political Psychology, 41(2), 303-322. https://doi.org/10.1111/pops.12615
Choma, B. L., Jagayat, A., Hodson, G., &amp;amp; Turner, R. (2018). Prejudice in the wake of terrorism: The role of temporal distance, ideology, and intergroup emotions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mock Social Media Website Tool</title>
      <link>https://arvinsroom.github.io/mock-social-media-website-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arvinsroom.github.io/mock-social-media-website-tool/</guid>
      <description>Background Developed in collaboration with Dr. Becky Choma and Carson Pun, the Mock Social Media Website aims to be an open-source comprehensive tool for conducting social media research by simultaneously allowing the researchers to do the following:
 Collect detailed behavioural data on social media behaviour  Know which posts participants liked, shared, replied to, any comments they made or added to their shares, what links they clicked, and more   Experimentally manipulate the contents and design of the platform  Specify every aspect of the posts that participants see, alter the features on the website, and randomly assign participants to experimental conditions which can present different posts or features to participants   Engage participants in an highly ecologically-valid user interface  In addition to using participant-submitted information to build their profiles, the website is designed with modern web design trends in mind to hopefully make participants believe that it is a real (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Interests</title>
      <link>https://arvinsroom.github.io/research-interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arvinsroom.github.io/research-interests/</guid>
      <description>Generally Broadly, my research focuses on intergroup attitudes and political behaviour in online contexts.
I&amp;rsquo;m interested in investigating how the design elements of Internet- and technology-enabled social spaces impact our attitudes and interactions; as well as how they can be modified to promote more positive social outcomes.
 Understanding Online Sexism Many of the ways that the Internet has allowed us to connect with one another are being co-opted to target women online.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
